People thinking this doesn't affect you...
Prepare for impact.
A strategy is needed for victory.
And I don't want to have mercy.
It's Hat! He infiltrated!
Don't kill him! He's an Ajin!
The situation of the Ajin on Japan
is going to change.
My name is Satou. I am an Ajin.
For the...
...Happiness.
You see...
I like to kill.
We are finally at the start point.
Not even us fight against the government.
This is not a fight, it's a war.
A taller building has been blown down, and has destroyed Grand Pharmaceuticals!
T-This...
God damnit!
The ambulances aren't here yet?
There's another wounded here!
Well, guys...
You don't think this is over, do you?
I-It's Satou!
The strongest soldiers in this country are...
The Police Special Assault Team.
So, if I beat them, I could name myself the strongest soldier of this country.
All of Japan is watching this battle! We can't lose!
Neither he.
Then...
It's show time!
Tiring!
That was
These are the images of what just happened to the Grand Pharmaceuticals Headquarters.
This was the Hattori building.
The Hattori building was a skyscraper built recently.
And this is the situation of Grand Pharmaceuticals, which was destroyed by this building.
Situation is somewhat confusing,
but the plan is the same.
Neutralize the target.
Spread out!
They have rubber armor!
And helmets.
It's impossible to kill one of those
unless you're pretty close.
Good.
This is war.
It's incredible.
At this rate, all of Japan will be watching this.
These are aerial images of the incident.
This incident hasn't had yet any response from the government.
But we believe that the perpetrator was the man known as Satou.
How unlucky for this company.
With this they'll definitely go bankrupt.
This is what happens when you let loose the Ajin.
They are beasts.
Ah, Kita-san...
What's going on? Why do you have that face?
You come here to talk about Yamanaka-san's grandson?
I've told you several times we can trust him!
There's new information about this case.
There are live transmissions of the man known as Satou being streamed from the internet.
On "Ajin.net".
Live at the crash site
The live stream...
Looks like it's coming from the place of the attack!
Live at the crash site
What's going on?
By any chance...
Did you have anyone you knew over there?
I don't care about the people!
I'm talking about money!
The accountants said...
That the actions were a safe investment!
That's what they told me!
Kita-san! Calm down!
My retirement and my saves...
I invested everything on Grand Pharmaceuticals!
God damn it!
Kita-san!
How are you planning to catch him?
Won't that end the same way it did in the laboratories?
We won't use numbing bullets.
The use of numbing bullets is forbidden.
It's not possible to use them openly,
same goes for the Anti-Ajin squad.
Even worse if the images are being streamed.
Fuck me! You use numbing pills with animals!
Those cases must be handled by a specialist.
It's the same with the Ajin.
And also...
This situation is different from the attack to the laboratory.
The incident of Nakamura Shin'ya.
The frat phenomenon won't be present.
Looks like you think this happened because you killed that Ajin multiple times, but...
That is a small, yet big mistake.
We call this phenomenon "Frat".
It's a phenomenon that is originated when there are too many resurrections and too many feelings involved.
Now that we know that frat has nothing to do with killing Ajin multiple times,
you just need to carry out my method.
After warning us so much, will you just kill it in the end?
Kill him?
No.
We won't stop killing him.
Do it.
What?
Proceed.
Looks like you changed your method, Tosaki...
Group number 2, proceed.
Number 3, go!
Shoot every 3 seconds,
don't let him revive.
Incessant shoots started moments ago.
Are them from the perpetrator?
There's no clear vision but we can see there are lots of corps.
Surrounding who its thought to be the culprit.
Looks like the corps won't stop shooting the culprit.
Is this a new method against the Ajin?
The corps keep shooting him.
So, will the strategy work?
Four-Eyes.
The culprit is on the ground!
The firing doesn't seem to stop.
Good!
Keep it up!
The shots keep going.
Could it be Satou, the Ajin the one being killed?
Don't get cocky now.
This'll end badly.
Proceed!
Carry him!
Fast! Hurry up! Come on!
Done!
Get out.
Lets take him in while we shoot him.
Hat isn't moving.
So easily...
It's obvious.
They're 20 PSAT members.
It's different from fighting simple guards.
Well...
Looks like he underestimated the humans.
If he can't die...
We just need to stop him from reviving.
Take him! We don’t want him to revive.
Shoot at my order.
Those are his allies! They’re shooting at us!
Adjust 2mm.
Ok...
Shields!
Gen-kun! Takahashi-kun!
I know...
Don’t let him revive!
Do something against the snipers!
The handcuffs are off.
Now we only need to give him a chance to revive.
Sniper 1 coming in, we've identified the targets as Ajin.
They're at my 22:00 in the rooftop of a building.
Sniper 2, we've identified the target.
Sniper 3, we've identified the target.
Good, let's kill them.
We've neutralized the enemy.
Okay, let's keep going.
Hurry up! We're almost there!
What do we do with the other one?
Don't shoot, he surrendered.
There are 3 snipers.
To the south.
On the rooftop of the north building.
And also in the last floor of the Mizuno building.
Got it.
Sniper 1, we're being shot.
Looks like there's another sniper.
No...
Is that...?
Do they really exist?
Sniper 1, what's going on!?
Number one has fallen.
It's the IBM! Get ready!
God dammit!
Where is it?
I found it! There is it!
It stopped... It stopped!
Good...
You're so slow you couldn't even hit him.
I won't be able to use it for some time.
The last place is...
I'll have to run a bit...
Open the vehicle!
Wake up already! If we don't cover
him, they'll take him away!
1 and 2 have fallen. We can't keep killing them.
Let's fall back!
Not yet.
I'll disable his rifle.
Aim to the one that's carrying the stretcher.
We have to give him a chance.
Ok...
I'll make the one in front to fall.
You can shoot.
Affirmative.
Dumbass! What are you doing?
Shit!
I hit him!
What is that?
You should shoot to them with both hands, Tanaka-san.
I know.
It's no use! It got spoiled!
How's Satou doing?
I'm looking at him!
Get out!
Good morning!
Shut up!
God dammit! It was useless.
Please...
That was close, you almost had me.
Awesome!
Do it, Satou!
That man...
Is not human!
He's a monster!
Don't be so noisy.
Shoot him.
Here we go!
Shoot him!
Ah... That was tiring!
There, Satou's there!
Let's follow him!
I don't like it...
The helicopter has been destroyed!
Could it have been affected by the bullets?
They just fell to the street and are being rescued.
What's the report on Satou?
Where is Satou?
It's impossible. Part of the camera system has been hacked.
We believe Satou defeated all troops.
It was useless.
Looks like you were tricked.
This is the start of the game.
Kei-kun... Give me a hand for a bit!
The search for the survivors is still being carried.
This incident caused by Satou has left many victims.
The position of company regarding their anti-terrorism measures is being discussed.
The company is in trouble.
My retirement...
What will happen with my life?
About this incident, the police will give a communicate in a few hours.
There's a 100 million yen reward for the person who captures an Ajin.
And we think there are already–
100 million?
These are the Ajin currently being searched by the police, and suspected of participating on this attack.
I'm Yamaka's grandson, I live in the village down the mountain.
I'm really sorry...
That boy!
To be continued
Next episode
crazy.
Satou,
you are