What’s going on!?
Kill him at once!
He’s not dying!
It’s only one enemy!
It must be the monster.
Our bullets are useless against him!
Don’t fuck me! Aim for his head!
Go, kill him!
I will!
Hey.
Don’t let your guard down.
It’s the Soldier of God!
Don’t let your guard down!
What’s this “Soldier of God”!? Take this! Take this! Take this...
I killed God!
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry Up! Hurry Up!
The history
of relationship we never had
You’re going to your test on Saturday, right?
How are you feeling?
I’m fine.
I can expect a good result, right?
Yes.
Don’t worry.
Thanks for the food.
I’m leaving.
Nagai-kun, do you study this early?
Yeah, I don’t want to waste my time.
Incredible, as expected from someone who wants to be a doctor.
Those who study medicine study different.
Why do I have to bear with his sarcasm?
I’m just giving my best to be a better person.
Kai.
Do you know him?
Of course not.
He’s a weird guy.
Yes he is.
Imagine he was an Ajin.
It’s hard to believe he’s a human like us.
That’s something that doesn’t have to do with us.
Well, open your books in page 247.
About the discovery of the Ajin.
This is apart from the entrance exam.
As human beings, we must try to understand.
I’ll be ignoring this part.
As you all know,
Ajin are immortal creatures.
It is said that they can’t die.
Although that’s not completely proven.
Among other things, it is said that they have very characteristic voices,
but the information hasn’t been disclosed to the public...
Look, an experiment with an Ajin.
An experiment?
It must be a hoax.
The first contact with an Ajin was in Africa, 17 years ago.
The year you were born in.
He was an immortal soldier, known as “Soldier of God” in that place.
Once he was caught by the American Army, the truth was discovered.
Although there were efforts to hide it,
the importance of the issue didn’t allow it.
At present day, it has been verified the existence of 46 all around the world,
and in Japan there are 2 of them.
It has been thought that there are Ajin that have not been located.
At the end of the day, it’s known
that they are Ajins if they don’t die.
Although, the possibility of an Ajin being in this place...
Isn’t 0.
Watanabe-kun.
I heard they give a lot of money as reward if you catch an Ajin.
The money thing must be a rumor,
but there must be some kind of reward.
For example, the ownership of a captured pre—
Prey?
Nagai-kun, do you have any questions?
N-No, it’s nothing.
You must have a question.
Um... Ajin aren’t human?
Huh? That’s obvious.
They’re a new species.
You’re right.
Now, about the use of the Ajin.
I should take care of this type of relationships.
An experiment with an Ajin.
This is horrible.
This is like...
Onii-chan.
Why has it died?
Mom said it was a defective product.
If you’re a defective product, you die?
It was sick, there was nothing we could do.
TL Note: I think that he’s referring to Ajins in this part.
Now that I think about it... Why do they die?
Even, without dying...
Who are you?!
You seem fine.
I’m not so bad.
If I was good, I wouldn’t be here.
I see...
So... What’re you doing here? Shouldn’t you be in your reinforcement academy?
We made a tomb for a dog when we were kids.
Do you remember that?
If you remember something...
Just as I thought...
It’s impossible for you to come without needing something.
Have you seen Kai-san lately?
Eh?
No, I haven’t.
I want to see Kai-san.
Kai, how is it?
I got it!
Incredible! It’s a Nokogiri scarab!
Kei-chan, give me your phone.
W-Why?
I will erase Kaito’s e-mail.
If you want to become a good human being,
you must choose better the people you get along with.
And to think we were such good friends...
Well... We’re all occupied now.
My brother should become a “good human being”, right?
Um... Eri, do you really not remember a thing?
When we did the tomb for the dog—
I don’t remember things that happened so long ago!
Why don’t you just go? Don’t you have things to do?
Nagai-san, It’s time to extract blood.
Oh, those are nice.
Throw them to the trash.
Become a good human being...
I’ve been doing just the necessary to achieve that.
I’ve chosen only what I need.
And there was when...
Ah!
The things that are not necessary...
Oh? Nagai-kun?
Must be deleted.
Was that...?
The light was red!
He’s at fault!
No!
An Ajin...
H-He’s one of them.
I-I really am... One of them...
N-N-No!
I’m not... I am...
I’m not!
I am human!
I believe you.
We are friends, right?
A great reward...
Ajin aren’t human?
Of course not.
What did he...!?
No... No!
No!
Oh, you. You got a sec?
Do you know Nagai Kei?
Don’t know him.
What did he do?
That kid, looks like he is an Ajin, an Ajin!
Really! I saw how he came back to life!
Yes!
Oh...?
I don’t care about this.
Well, it’s okay if you don’t know anything.
It can’t be... Are they home!?
Where...? Where should I go to?
Someone... Someone... It can’t be!
Kei, look!
Kai...
Kei, I’ve been waiting for you.
Kai! Um...
What should... What should I do?
Calm down, where are you right now?
Now?
I’m in...
I believe you.
Um... Well...
Don’t worry.
Kai...
Under the tree we caught that scarab once.
I’ll go now.
Kai!?
I’ve found the Ajin, I need reinforcements!
Wait! Get back here!
I won’t let him catch me! I won’t let him catch me!
I won’t hurt you, just surrender.
Don’t move! Don’t move.
I’ve found the Ajin, near the Tsuki temple, I’ve found the Ajin.
Ajin?
Kai!
Wait! Don’t say names.
Can you get up?
Yes.
Let’s run!
The Ajin is running! I repeat...
The Ajin is running! He seems to have a partner.
I need reinforcements!
Are you fine?
Yeah!
We’re in front of the Ajin’s house,
the third Ajin in Japan has been discovered, at the moment he’s fugitive.
This small town is in panic because of it.
I had my suspicions,
he didn’t seem like a human.
He can be an Ajin, but he’s still a brat.
He won’t get far.
Hurry up and catch him.
Sorry for the delay I’m Araki, from Saitama’s Police.
Sorry for the delay. I’m Araki, from Saitama’s Police.
You’re underestimating your situation.
Even if you tell me that...
We have enough people working on this...
This is an incident of national degree.
Yes...
The treaties are equal around the world. If because of your incompetence, another country captures Nagai Kei...
You know what’ll happen, right?
Use the double, no...  Triple the personnel.
Do everything you need to find him!
A new Ajin, Nagai Kei.
We can’t let him get away.
I won’t let them catch me.
To be continued
Next Episode
Why did
things turn out this way? I didn’t do anything wrong.