The directors are not impressed, Tosaki.
What should I do?
At this rate, they’ll end up eliminating me.
I don’t mind. I don’t have any
more attachments to this world.
My name is Satou.
I am an Ajin.
The government uses the Ajin to carry out inhumane experiments.
I will be holding a protest!
The place will be in front of the Ministry of Labor, Health and Wellness!
It’s today, right? What do you have in mind?
Nothing’s going to happen, people won’t be moved by something like this.
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
You all going to protest?
No way man–––
Is that even real? It was so cringy it made me laugh lol
This strategy wasn’t made to call out people.
It was to bring Ajin together.
Thank you for coming.
Now I’ll tell you the real meeting point.
You brought the FK’s, right?
I don’t care how miserable everyone will become,
I’ll achieve my objective.
I will make you tell me everything.
Everything you know.
I’ve gotten used to the pain, but...
Drowning...
Is the worst.
I think helping others...
Isn’t something I should do often.
Is this everyone?
My name is Satou. Get up here.
What’s wrong with you!? You appeared suddenly!
This is bad...
She fell by herself, leave her alone.
Ah! Come on!
This is a good view!
This must be the first time that you...
have seen so much Ajin reunited.
Ah... Satou-san...
I’m still not your ally.
I would like you to
explain me, how do you plan
to make Ajin rights get respected.
He’s right.
I would like to know too.
I don’t have anything as a big plan as of right now.
I would only like to do everything I can,
with all my strength.
I would like you to be more detailed.
I’m talking about mass murder.
I gave a deadline in that broadcast.
The government that hides the truth...
The completely uninterested population...
I...
I don’t want to have any more mercy.
But in the end, we are only this many.
Do we have any chances of winning?
I’ll do it.
Are you idiots!?
That’s not what we should do!
Of course, I wasn’t expecting
to get everyone’s approval.
Uh... Who’s against this?
You and...
Those two.
Oh?
And you?
What will you do?
I’m against it...
Ah... I see. How unlucky.
Well... Those against this can leave.
Let’s go.
I won’t let you make stupid things.
I’ll make you stop at any cost.
Is he alright!?
Run!
Emergency Exit
Over there!
Run!
Are we going to leave everyone else behind?
If they catch us, who will stop Satou?
Huh? It isn’t opening! What do we do?
...Satou-san?
Your aim hasn’t improved at all...
You shot me...
I’m dying...
I-I’m really sorry.
But...
You did shot him in the centre.
What should I do with these?
Put them inside barrels,
and bury them underground.
Do you understand now?
Those are their real intentions!
What will happen to the others?
I’m guessing he’ll lock them!
Good...
I’ll see how devoted you are to me.
You will help Tanaka-kun.
Chase those who escaped and catch them.
And you...
I can’t run.
The muscles on my right leg
are weak since I was born.
Even when I revive, my leg will still be the same.
Then how can you help us?
That.
That rifle... The scope is a bit diverted to the right,
so you should aim a bit to the left.
Also, the gas capsule isn’t tight enough.
Seems like I’ve got more more knowledge than Tanaka-kun when it comes to guns and machinery.
Very good... Not bad...
Well... Let the game begin!
Should we keep going?
What should we do after getting out?
Continue with your normal life!
This is not your job!
Shit!
What do we do?
Over here!
Jump! I’ll buy you some time!
From here!?
Aren’t you an Ajin?
Jump at once!
If afraid of heights...
Listen. Since they can’t die,
it doesn’t matter how much the police does.
They will kill as much people as they want!
Even if you say that...
I have a family and a daughter!
I need to stop him, no matter what!
Then push me!
Do you think I can just push a boy!?
Oji-san!
We hit him!
Tanaka-san, do it!
He’s pretty bad...
Shut up.
You’re the only one I can count on.
Only you...
Can stop Satou.
W-Wait a moment!
Stop him at any cost.
Go!
Understood!
A little to the left...
Oji-san!
What?
Hurry up! Jump!
Y-Yes!
Really!?
These images were recorded yesterday
with a TV camera.
This man was pushed by something he couldn’t see.
So there were IBM.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, we couldn’t
determine the number, but...
Zoom in.
You won’t find any more than this.
No.
I’m talking about the
guy on the background.
It looks like he’s following
something with his eyes.
He can see the IBM.
This guy...
Is our clue.
He’s fast for running away.
Hey.
Satou’s strategy...
Do you think it’s good?
What again?
The goverment hides information about the Ajin,
to avoid a general panic.
But...
If you commit terrorist acts,
no matter what you do.
A hunt for Ajin will start.
Backed by all of the Japanese population.
Is it really alright for me to stay here?
It’s alright, since you brought me and also helped me with my stuff.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
After all, she has already seen my face...
It wouldn’t be a good idea to run away out of the blue.
I’m sorry for the delay. I’m sorry I can only offer you this.
In other news, about the Ajin who escaped
some days ago from the research lab.
The search for Nagai Kei continues.
The police, after expanding the number of scouters, is awaiting any information.
This problem originated from the suspicions of inhumane experiments on Ajin, followed by some misterious explosions.
How will this turn out?
I am not going to do anything stupid.
Young men go through a lot.
You’re Kei-kun, right?
I have a grandson almost your age.
His name is Ryuta, and it has been some years since I last saw him.
It’s a good moment to try new things.
It wasn't him...
Is that from an Ajin?
No... That wasn’t the direction Satou was.
Then...
Who is that?
Ah... It disappeared again.
Why does it disappear like that?
But... Now I know how to summon it.
Definitely, I shouldn’t help others.
With him, this is the fifth I release in a row.
Oh, my. Good Morning.
G-Good morning!
Look at you! You’re covered in blood!
Ah...! This, Uh... I fell!
An Ambulance!
I need to call an ambulance!
No! It’s not necessary.
That lady is pretty nosy.
I left it unlocked.
You are Nakano Kou-kun, right?
That’s right...
Hold!
Those bodyguards...
They were with professor Ogura, right?
Yeah.
Are they from the ministry?
That’s impossible.
They work for someone else.
I only hired them again.
They can do multiple jobs.
Among them, dirty work.
Shit! Will I have to jump again?
This is as far as you go.
This is bad! This is bad! This is bad!
You’re the only one who can stop Satou!
I know!
Shit...
What should we do?
Run him over.
If you don’t want to, let’s change seats.
We have been told there was a hurt young!
We didn’t think he was in such a bad state!
Been told...?
He’s laughing...
He must have hit his head.
We’re really sorry.
Investigate where are they taking him.
With those wounds, he’ll get admitted to the hospital.
His pulse has stopped, we didn’t make it.
Shit... The hemorrhage was too strong...
We’ve fixed everything so they take him in.
We need to take him anyways.
Shit! My only advantage was that
nobody knew I was an Ajin!
This is...
An Ajin different from Satou and the rest?
I’ve managed to release
him for longer than before, but...
Why does it disappear?
That’s my line.
How’re you going? Toukiyama-kun.
Ah, it’s ready.
I’m using one of the neighbors’ line and proxies on China and Russia to upload it.
They won’t find us.
Very well... It looks very good.
Thank you.
Hi! Seems like we meet again. I’m Satou, the Ajin.
This time I’m not talking about anything fun.
We’ve been corralled.
So we had to make a choice.
We’ll start creating a country where we can live based on strength.
Our first move will be next Wednesday at 15:00.
We’ll attack the Grand Medicine buildings.
I want to show our military power
to any still dubitative Ajin.
And to the people who think
this doesn’t concern them as well.
Finally, it will begin.
Prepare for impact.
To be continued
Next episode
Wait
I discussed again