Mass murders.
Run away!
You're the only one who can stop Satou!
Really!?
That guy in the background,
he can see the IBM passing by.
You're Nakano Kou-kun, right?
Don't move!
This is bad! This is bad! This is bad!
Run him over. If you don't want to, let's change seats.
That isn't the direction Satou was in.
Then, who's that?
People thinking this doesn't affect you.
Finally, it's about to begin.
Prepare for impact.
That was the threat uploaded to the internet by a man who calls himself Satou.
Satou, 10 days from now, at 15:00,
he will attack the Grand Pharmaceutical headquarters.
The police and other related entities,
are joining forces with the goal of securing the place.
According to the police,
the video was uploaded using proxies from China and Russia.
For this reason, determining the original location from where it was uploaded may be difficult.
There's also much speculation about the relation between Satou and the Ajin who escaped a few days ago, Nagai Kei...
And this concludes today's news.
Wait
I discussed again
Excuse me for the inconveniences...
Shut up.
I need to pee.
So annoying...
Nagai Kei?
Wait! Don't!
Serves you right.
What are you doing?
You're annoying, disobey my orders...
You are violent...
Shut up.
You shut up.
Damn it...
It would be great being able to control it like Satou-san.
On the other side, this is bad.
Who is he?
Is he...?
I am...
Nakano...
Nakano Kou.
You...
You are Nagai Kei, right?
The news said you dropped that guy from the building, but...
You were saving him...
Because you were fighting with Satou, right?
Do you know Satou's true character?
Yeah.
I've escaped from the government guys and Satou.
I don't have anyone else I can rely on.
Please, help me! I have to stop him.
We can't let him be!
Okay.
We can't talk here, let's go in deeper,
I'll show you the way.
Yeah.
I'm hungry...
Hey, do you have anything to eat?
I'll bring you something later.
This is what you asked me for.
I apologize for asking you such irrational things.
This isn't just "irrational".
Well?
It's fine.
Just with this will be enough.
Is it okay if we keep the car?
Yeah, I've purchased it under a dummy company name.
No one will find it.
Also, the other goods are ready.
It may even arrive today.
Man, you've really helped us.
Now then, we also have some goodies for you.
Is it okay for you to give us this much?
We have more people now.
Even for us, fighting against the government is a no-go.
Nekozawa-san...
This is not a fight...
It's a war.
Ah, dammit.
This is quite hard.
Oh, Kei-kun.
Going out again?
Ah, yeah. I'm going for a walk.
So slow.
Sorry for taking so long.
Some things took more than expected.
It's a silent place, isn't it?
Yeah, it's very good.
And to think they said on TV that
you ran away from the country.
Yeah.
I didn't even leave Tokyo.
How are you surviving?
I'm living in the house of someone called Yamanaka-san.
This is the safe place I finally could find.
Who is this kid?
Ah, shit...
Hi...
He's my grandson.
Granma, that sounds like a lie.
Ah... the one from Tokyo?
That's right...
My good for nothing son suddenly dumped his son on me.
He's so troublesome.
You say that but...
Aren't you feeling happy deep inside?
Boy, don't get in trouble with the police now.
Your grandma was worried sick about you the last time!
I'll do my best.
What kind of grandson did she have?
Nobody knows my face if I move just a little into the countryside.
Despite all the news about me.
Are you listening to me?
Yeah! Yeah!
I'm listening. I'm listening.
Nakano-kun.
Do you really want to fight Satou-san?
Why?
The media hasn't exposed you,
unlike me, that have been exposed all over the place.
I think you have more possibilities than me
to live in peace.
Even though, you still want to do it?
I have to!
I see...
I can't understand it.
Ibotengutake mushrooms,
you see a lot of them around here.
They're poisonous, but they taste good.
The poisoning symptoms will begin in about 20 minutes.
Abdominal pain, vomiting, hallucinations, seizures, disorientation,
and lastly, loss of consciousness.
There are ways to incapacitate you,
even if you're immortal.
This is my safe place.
I can't let you go around.
Now that you know where I am.
Nakano...
What a crazy guy.
In that direction is...
He's... trying to do the reset!
Wait! Let's talk again!
Second option, cerebral hit.
A mild hit would be a few seconds. A stronger one, several hours.
I could make him lose consciousness.
Wait a moment!
Now the jaw.
Dammit!
If that's what you want!
Then I'll do it!
I was popular in high school!
The King of Fighters?
He died?
Third option.
Drowning.
1... 2... 3...
Death by drowning has several stages.
A few seconds won't result.
From 30 seconds to a full minute, respiratory problems will manifest.
Spasms begin from 1 to 3 minutes.
Loss of consciousness, numbness...
106...
...107...
Death.
The point is that it takes time to die.
Okay, from now on this will be our new home.
You revived?
What's this place?
This place...
Is an abandoned truck.
Dumbass! Let me out!
Truth is, I'm being good.
I could have crippled you for life.
If you don't want to be reported, get me out of...
What?
I took your cellphone.
You seriously won't fight?
Satou will kill a lot of people!
Well, then why are you in Japan?
In any part of the world,
there are many people dying unfairly.
Why don't you save them?
Yeah... It doesn't matter what happens with other people.
That's not my problem.
Then why did you save that investigator?
I've been thinking about that too,
and I have come to a single conclusion.
It was something that gave me a benefit.
He understood the Ajin.
Also, working for the government gives him value.
He was worth dying 1 or 2 times to save.
Do you got any other questions?
Idiot. Let me out!
See ya.
I doesn't matter how much you scream.
Even the black ghost has trouble
breaking out of this.
There's a small hole, use it to do your business.
Ah, one more thing.
I'll bring you some magazines.
In an empty place,
a person's sanity will only last up to 72 hours.
God damnit! God damnit! God damnit!
What is he thinking?
What is wrong with him!?
Grand Pharmaceuticals Press Conference
That's why...
As I've said before.
Grand Pharmaceuticals Press Conference
The fact that we were doing experiments with the Ajin...
Is completely fake.
Grand Pharmaceuticals Press Conference
You've seen the video, right?
The one with Satou's warning message.
He's saying that the Grand Pharmaceutical is involved in these Ajin experiments.
That is...
A baseless lie.
And what about Nagai Kei, dropping a researcher from the roof of the lab?
That's right! He must have had a reason to!
Are you covering up the experiments?
Nagai Kei...
was already mentally unstable when he was brought to the facility.
This was the result of the
media and many heartless people–
Dammit! The media talks too much!
What do you plan to do, Tosaki?
It's true that the media can talk a lot,
but Japan's media has already lost its value.
Aside from a minority, the public realizes this and will ignore them.
And that minority is the loudest!
The idiots that belive stupid news.
Nevertheless, that's not something that we should be discussing right now.
Then, what should we discuss?
The most important thing is to fight against Hat.
What are you talking about?
On top of letting Hat infiltrate here
You even let the sample run away.
That's right! How much do you think we've lost?
Why haven't you been fired?
Keep barking.
This people do nothing but complain.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry I'm late.
The identity verification took some time.
Sokabe...
Why are you here?
It's a bit hard to tell the person who mentored me,
but the ministry called me.
To be your potential successor.
Working under you finally paid off.
About time.
Starting today, I will be supervising your work here,
and sending reports about your performance.
In the case that a problem is created...
So, you'll replace me.
No, that'd be a headache.
This is my warning to you.
Once you cross this line, there's no going back.
This isn't the time to act all superior, is it?
The police will be in charge of defending Grand Pharmaceutical headquarters.
But we, the Ajin Management Committee,
will participate as consultants.
We don't have much left.
Until then, will you be able
to find something against the IBM?
I hope you can.
Why don't you tell us?
I'm talking about the IBM.
Old man...
I want to smoke one.
I've brought your cigarettes.
Do you think I'll smoke that?
What do you want to get?
You have been declared dead already.
Like an Ajin.
Why won't you tell us a thing?
Didn't you talk big in front
of the other investigators?
It's simple, don't you understand?
Any cigarette besides FK is shit,
baldie.
So the queen is finally back.
Maybe this man really knows nothing.
Doesn't matter how much I hit him, he won't talk.
In the first place, it will be hard to determine if he's telling us the truth.
Show him, Shimomura-kun.
Yes, sir.
These are the things of the bodyguard.
He wasn't a simple bodyguard.
Special agent?
Ogura Ikuya was received to this country,
not for his work as a biophysicist.
What this man says,
may not have any theory or basis,
but it just happens to be correct.
His ideas contributed largely to
a certain field of research.
Namely, IBM countermeasures.
His information is valuable.
That's insane.
What else from a country that
only cares about results?
Shall I break one more?
At least leave me two.
A smoker is as good as dead without them.
W-Wait! It was a joke.
You want to talk now?
I need three.
So I can flick the ashes.
What is it that you want?
You don't feel pain?
Do you think you've become an Ajin?
Physical pain is something...
I can handle...
Tosaki-san.
This guy won't talk.
Why?
Because he's crazy.
That's right, four-eyes.
With only this, I...
I won't speak.
I only have one condition to speak.
Only one.
Give me an FK.
FK? Really?
I've told you from the start.
There is one in my car.
Bring it.
Right now!
Disgusting.
Well...
Where would you like to start?
To be continued
Next episode
Starts
It
Decaying
the moment
it's created