I’ve found the Ajin, I need reinforcements!
Wait! Get back here!
I’ve found the Ajin, near the Tsuki temple,
I’ve found the Ajin.
Let’s run!
The third Ajin in Japan has been discovered, at the moment he’s fugitive.
You’re underestimating your situation.
This is an incident of national degree.
Use the double, no...  Triple the personnel.
We can’t let him get away.
There’s no doubt! He’s the Ajin!
It’s a hundred million!
They’ll really give it to us?
How did this happen?
I’m not at fault!
Be careful with the Ajin’s voice.
I’ve heard it puts you in some kind of paralysis,
and it gets impossible to move for a few seconds.
Kai! Can you stand up? Run!
We got them!
If they don’t die, then run over them!
It’s because people like you that...
It’s because of you that...!
I can’t move...
An Ajin is nothing more than
a boring being that cannot die.
Is that what you think?
I need you to improve your
senses and question what you saw.
When the privileges as an Ajin were given to you.
I’ll show you, anyway.
That is why I came to save you, Tanaka-kun.
It
Is
no use anymore?
The third Ajin found in Japan is still on the run.
The news about the discovery of a new Ajin...
They say he’s an Ajin.
Ah... It seems that we can get
a lot of money if we catch him.
Really?
It’s morning already.
At this rate, they’ll end up finding us.
We have to hide while we can.
When we get there, we’ll be fine.
Our hideout is an abandoned
cabin in the mountains.
Kai likes using his motorcycle,
so he knows this kind of places.
If we go over there, we’ll be even-minded.
But then... What will we do later on?
The situation is worse than I thought.
All of Japan… No, all the people around the world must know of my existence at this point.
There will be people all around the world trying to catch me.
What’s wrong?
He stopped...
I’m lucky.
Here he comes!
I see...
They’re two, I’ll catch up to them quickly.
His accomplice is also a kid.
I’ll be able to catch him.
Have they gotten any information?
They still haven’t finished.
Also, what’re you doing here?
We’ll leave at this, for the moment.
You look really tired.
I’m so sorry...
One last question.
I would like to get a sincere answer.
How do you feel now? Knowing that your son is an Ajin.
I didn’t thought my son... Wouldn’t be human.
I see.
This was a waste of time...
How’s the search for Nagai Kei going?
A woman said she heard an Ajin’s scream
in one of the mountains on the way to Yamanashi.
I didn’t think there would be witnesses this soon.
His accomplice is most likely a novice, or a normal citizen.
Yes...
If he was a professional or an external agent,
it would have been impossible for them to be seen.
If he’s a novice that wants money,
we’ll probably find him easily.
Do you really think so?
What do you mean?
I don’t think someone would help him for money...
Do you think someone would want to help an Ajin for something but money?
There he is!
Wait.
But...!
Calm down.
“Hat” has been seen near the household of the Nagai,
communicate with the special squad.
Don’t waste time.
“Hat” must be hunting down Nagai Kei, too.
It’s possible. Anyway, be careful at all times.
We won’t follow him now.
The worst case-scenario.
We need to avoid the worst of situations.
But if he hunts down Nagai Kei,
a lot of innocent people will die again.
Kai! He’s about to reach us!
Can you use your voice?
But there’s the noise of the motor, and also you...
We don’t have other choice.
Although we don’t know if it’ll work out.
If he falls, we win.
Alright.
Let’s go!
Wait a moment. If I do it at this speed,
that person will die...
That was easy.
Kai...
Kai!
That hurts...
There’s no coverage.
Please...
Call an ambulance.
He’s a human!
It’s your fault.
It’s my fault?
If I hadn’t asked him for help...
This wouldn’t have happened?
Get up! Walk.
You can’t get up?
It’s not that.
If only him didn’t exist...
Kai would be alive.
If only him... If only him... If only him didn’t exist!
Kai!
I’m glad!
I faked I was dead.
This doesn’t hurt at all.
Well, let’s go.
I’ll keep his motorcycle.
Kei.
I think we can’t go on.
What’re you talking about?
My leg is broken.
And with what just happened, it’s more than clear.
If we’re together, you’ll...
Kei.
I guess that...
And Ajin and a human shouldn’t—
Kei!
You are a human.
I think that.
That’s why, if you run away to a place
no one knows, but me,
you’ll still be human.
Wait a moment.
I’ll patch you up.
No...
No!
I’ve understood with the things that have happened.
That I’m not... Human anymore.
It hurts... It hurts...
But even if I tell him to leave me here, he wouldn’t listen.
With this leg I’ll put Kai in danger.
What do I do? What should I do?
Think like one...
Like an... Like an Ajin.
Kei! Don’t–
With this, my leg is healed. Let’s go, Kai.
He looks scared,
of a lot of people dying again.
Or maybe they want to avoid another Nakamura Shin’ya incident.
That’s why they won’t take any big actions.
Then, what will we do now, Satou-san?
We have to show him the way.
We’ll encounter Nagai Kei.
Can you help me?
Tanaka-kun.
Nagai Kei...
I am... an Ajin.
Are you sure you’re okay?
What’re you talking about?
That was going too far.
It’s alright.
I’m more relaxed, and my head is alright.
That’s not the issue.
On the other side, you worry me more.
If a human dies, he cannot come back to life.
What’ll you do from now on?
Hey...
If it’s on, it’ll give our location to the police.
That doesn’t work anymore.
In any case...
I would like to go somewhere safe.
If you want to go somewhere safe,
you need not to leave this mountain.
When food runs out, I’ll go for more.
If I recall correctly, the number of people
disappeared last year was 2396.
About 294 of them disappeared in the mountains.
You even know that?
It was announced in the news.
If every year, almost 300 people disappear in the mountains,
maybe they won’t find us.
If that’s the case...
But... We can’t.
I want to live in peace.
I don’t want to give away my peaceful
style of life for being an Ajin.
Kyuushu...
My granpa lives in Kyuushu.
It’s a village isolated from human contact,
so no one is going to notice.
That’s why...
Even while being an Ajin?
Maybe you’ll be able to live relaxed there.
You’re right.
Maybe that’s better.
Good, it’s decided.
I’ll go buy some stuff.
Is there something you want?
Ah, I would like a tooth brush.
Looks like they lost him.
However, he hasn’t been around that much.
In this situation, doing things bigger,
would be something risky for him.
So, what should I...?
I have that meeting.
People won’t stop complaining about money and time.
Go here, I’ll leave this to you.
Act calm.
Don’t say unnecessary things.
Yes.
A village in Kyuushu.
Humans that don’t get bothered by Ajins...
It’s impossible that humans like that exist.
Plus, we still have 100 kilometers ahead of us.
It will be impossible to get there.
No only for an Ajin. It would be very dangerous for a human.
I think it’s time to say goodbye to Kai.
What is this?
It’s time to say goodbye...
I don’t know anything about it!
Besides, a detective came yesterday too!
I’m not from the police.
I’m from the Ajin’s Management Committee.
The managing committee makes investigations on Ajin,
and handles them.
I don’t understand.
I’m asking about the personal life of Nagai Kei.
I shouldn’t...
Be going through all this.
It’s because you’re the sister of Nagai Kei.
Eriko-san.
I’m sorry to disturb you in this state, but I hope you can help me.
It’s gross.
To know that a family member that I though was human was in my family.
It’s too gross.
I... know someone who had
an Ajin for family member.
So?
I couldn’t know what that person felt like.
Nonetheless,
I don’t want there to be more people
like them, or like you.
It’s because of that, that I want to clear some things out about the Ajin.
What do you mean by that?
To know how they’re born,
to know if they’re truly immortal,
and to know if they’re truly not human.
It doesn’t matter if it’s insignificant.
There was nothing about your brother that called your attention?
Even if you ask me that...
There’s something, not very important,
but if I tell you, you’ll go?
Sure.
Time ago...
When our dog died, he said something strange.
Who are you?
Go away, Erika! There’s a ghost!
Ghost?
He isn’t coming...
He’s coming out...
There was nothing,
but he claimed there was a ghost.
Nagai Kei said he saw the black ghost?
I didn’t know if it was black or not.
I said too much.
Tosaki-san will get angry at me.
What’s with her?
But, in those times,
Kei and me played a lot,
So did...
Kai-san.
Could it be that the accomplice is...?
Did you say something?
No... nothing.
If you remembered something,
no matter how insignificant it is–
What happe–?
To be continued
Next episode
Black
Have you
seen the
Ghost?