This is—
A bandage?
We’ve given him to the humans
to bring out vengeful feelings
and hate against them.
How cruel...
Why do I have to go through something like this?
So now you understand.
You’re nothing more than an cocky idiot who
only asks for help when in need.
That’s it... Do it...
Find your true self!
There’s an intruder!
Hat has entered!
Has he come to save Nagai?
After abandoning him...
Seriously, why all the fuss?
If the great Ogura Ikuya is here—
Now, Nagai-kun.
I came to save you.
Satou-san...
I’m sorry for causing you trouble...
This mission...
Has been a failure.
Well, let’s go. We can’t stay longer.
Yeah...
shit
I’ll beat the
out of you
Does that draw your attention?
Not especially.
Protecting this place was these people's work.
Besides, he’s dead.
It’s true.
On the other hand.
I want to get out of here at any cost.
So I’ll let you take care of me.
Good, let’s hurry up then.
This kid...
Made me remember the confusion I felt the first time I saw him.
He seemed worried about his sister,
but there was something false about it.
This kid has something strange,
besides being an Ajin.
I thought the mission had failed,
but I think I’ll observe him a little longer.
Don’t shoot!
We’re not security guards!
We have to keep going.
Eh...
Are you going to kill them?
Yes.
We can’t let anyone alive.
It’s just that...
I’m sorry to do this after you saved me, but...
They’re unarmed...
I think it’s not necessary to kill them.
They could be hiding narcotic guns.
Then, we could leave them blind...
Or break their arms...
Nagai-kun...
Just as I thought...
You are a failure.
You have shot me...
I’m so sorry.
It was an accident.
Nagai...
You...
I’ll kill you!
The IBM is matter.
Then why can’t we see it?
Can you see this?
It’s time to learn.
The light emitted from its source gets reflected in matter.
The eye senses it and that’s why we see things.
Then, why is glass transparent?
That’s because glass is made of substances that let light go through.
Normal glasses have a
transparency rate of 80% to 90%.
The IBM has a transparency rate of 100%.
It’s made of an unknown matter.
Don’t take it so seriously, Riku-san.
He is the man who does nothing
but spit out baseless hypothesis.
In Japan, at least.
The fact that you have been recognised by a dumb country.
Does that make you so happy, Ikuya-kun?
It’s because of that mindset
that you can’t step it up.
Kishi-sensei.
He won’t come out...
The repair room is out of our sight.
Tosaki-san...
I won’t need to fight?
Of course not.
If they get here, who will protect me?
You stay here.
Don’t go anywhere.
Yes...
Where did he go?
We don’t have any weapons, or a map.
How can I escape?
Who would have thought
I’d have to hide with an Ajin.
Stop!
He has saved us.
Fuck me! In the first place he was the one that brought him here.
How many people do you think have died because of him.
I haven’t killed them.
In the first place, if we keep this up...
It’s not like I’ve forgotten what you did to me.
I’ll send you back to the lab!
I don’t want to! I don’t want to go back!
I’ll get out of here at any cost.
You also want to get out, right?
Our objectives are the same.
We’re even.
I’ll be the bait so you can get out of here.
In exchange, you’ll show me the escape route,
so I can get out of here safely.
Are you really going to be the bait?
In the end, I can’t die.
That’s not true...
Stop it.
It’s settled.
Nagai-kun.
Are you listening?
You must be confident on your
inability to die, I’m guessing.
I wasn’t exaggerating when I said
I was going to kill you.
Ajin can die.
Stop talking about that...
Although that depends on how you die.
The resurrection of an Ajin starts
with the biggest chunk of flesh.
However, the flesh that has gone
too far away is not recovered.
Instead, new flesh is created.
If that happens
with your head...
I’ll promise you.
I’ll cut off your head,
and then put it in front of your body.
I’ll make you see how a new head grows, until you die.
The question is, who will be you then?
The new head that will be created,
or the head that's right here?
With this, it all ends.
I’ll make you regret to death.
For killing me.
Nagai...
Kei-kun.
You don’t need to do it.
I’ll do it.
I’ll make you both get outside.
It’s what I have to do.
Maybe.
He’ll try to hit me in the back.
If he hits me there, I’ll be able to revive.
What’re you doing?
Didn’t we promise it to him?
If you help him escape, I'm not responsible
for what happens next!
I shouldn’t have...
Goddamnit... Why does this has to happen to me?
What is this?
Why is there so much of this?
It’s time.
I’ll kill you.
This is...
Nagai-kun’s ghost.
How about this?
It’s true that the black ghost can cast some words...
But this is just ridiculous.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
A human made with unknown matter?
And how's that related to the Ajin's immortality?
Why do people eat tangerines?
Serves you right.
That thing saved me.
People can’t make vitamin C by themselves.
That’s why they have to get it from fruits.
The black ghost...
The Ajin can draw those things out.
When those who die from malnutrition revive,
they can even produce those nutrients.
But that doesn’t have anything to do with their immortality!
It’s impossible for it to not be related
to the unknown matter.
What are you doing?
I’ll survive in this room.
If he follows the lines,
he might catch up to us!
Goodness.
Wh-What?
Can you see it?
When I’m under intense emotions, sometimes humans are able to see him.
It’s the bloodlust, or something like that.
Help!
I’m sorry, but I can’t do that, because...
I like to kill.
Nagai-kun! Over here!
What are you doing here?
I have to show you the way out of here.
That isn’t necessary.
I see.
I hope I can die from this height.
But I wasn’t waiting you only because of that.
When you get down there,
I can take you somewhere with my car.
What?
I’ve always been telling myself that this is my job,
but truth is, I have done really bad things.
Besides, there’s something else I’d like you to know.
You... Are just as how you were.
During the experiment, your head wasn’t cut, not even once.
There were also no traces of brain tissue at the crash site.
I just wanted you to know that.
Why do you get worried so easily for other people?
Can you understand human pain?
I’ve never... been worried for someone else.
Nagai-kun... Just as I thought, you’re interesting.
Including the personality that your sister talked about.
So they both asked you,
how your brother was.
Yes.
And what did you tell them?
He is...
The worst.
The wind is strong...
Let’s hide.
The worst?
It can’t b—
He’s the worst.
His real personality is rational,
and extremely cold.
He...
Is like that.
If he’s dead, I don’t know how to save him.
Shortest distance is...
Over there!
How unlucky, I ran out of bullets.
Is he still alive?
This is the last level, Nagai-kun!
Goddamnit!
Hey ghost! Come out again!
Come out again!
It came!
I’m under the rain but... Well, it doesn’t matter.
Is he aiming for the head?
You aim to the head too!
Why did you always make jokes like that?
Oh, very good. So it can ignore your orders too.
I only played with him because it made me sad to see him alone.
Don’t say things from so long ago...
Nagai-kun...
Run...
No.
Why?
I didn’t want to get related with anyone,
nor I had that need.
Neither I cared about others.
But...
I want to save you.
That’s why...
I’m going to let you fall from here.
It’s the only choice.
If he manages to fall in the grass,
the chances of survival are greater.
It’s him! It’s Nagai Kei!
It looks like he wants to drop a member
from the research team.
Is he taking him as hostage?
What are you thinking? At this rate he’ll run away!
Kouma Riku-san...
What do you want?
How much...
How much time would it take
the Anti-Ajin special force to be ready?
Don’t joke with that!
That’s nothing more than a special force that appeared
when the existence of the Ajin was discovered!
Please, Kouma Riku-san.
We have yet to find a solution to this situation.
It’s impossible to make the troops go—
This is our chance!
What do you mean by that?
Why didn’t hat use his IBM today?
Don’t you think it’s strange?
He wasn’t able to use it today.
I don’t know the reason, but that possibility is high.
There’s a big difference between this assault and the one from Tanaka.
There won’t be another chance like this!
Please, Riku-san!
Bend your legs.
Here we go!
W-Wait.
Can you see it?
What's that?
How are you going to fight now?
Aim to the head too...
These were the memories from...
I could see some of Nagai-kun's memories.
So that’s what happens when the heads collide.
Nagai-kun...
Do it!
Did he let him go?
Understood. It’s ok.
Nevertheless, if this theory is correct...
Professor Ogura, you were listening, right?
IBM is not as efficient as you guys think.
There are lots of conditions to use it.
Can you see it, Nagai-Kun?
That river is a channel that leads
to the sea on rainy days.
If you get in it, maybe you’ll make it.
Professor, please refrain from giving out
information about the Ajin.
Ah, it’s true.
So... No comments.
Understood.
Nagai Kei has jumped to the river!
What does that mean?
I’m leaving. The sample has run away.
Nagai Kei has jumped from the rooftop to the river.
After he let go to someone that looked like an investigator, he jumped to the river.
The water of the river, because of the rain...
To be continued
Next episode
Be
sure
to hide.