I’m not human anymore!
You are a human, I think that.
We have to show him the way.
We need to avoid the worst of situations.
There was nothing, but he
claimed there was a ghost.
She fainted... How boring.
What’s going on?
Pretending to be human...
You...
Get out of here!
a black
Did you see
ghost in the spring?
Do you like games, Tanaka-kun?
In video games, if you have 100 lives,
you can revive 99 times.
Not to mention,
video games have cheats.
If you could use two lifes at the same time...
What would happen with that remaining life?
That’s what I mean.
If you get the catch of it, you’ll be able to use it too.
Did you know that Ajin...
Use the bigger chunks of meat as a base to regenerate?
However, the chunks that are far apart
from the body will not be picked up.
In their place, new chunks are made.
If that chunk was the head...
Don’t you get the creeps?
You don’t?
What?
You also have one...
How long has it been since I last released Kuro-chan?
What should I do in this cases? I’ve never been taught to fight one of those...
I’ve never fought against this... How can I beat it?
In the first place, can one beat it?
What links me with this thing is probably my head.
Knowing it has human form, I should go to...
Did it hit me...
Below?
What?
What’s happening? It won’t regenerate! The transmission of the vision is...
My conciousness...
It’s going out... Is it disintegrating?
No...
Cancelation?
Physical impacts make effect!
It broke!
Goddammit! Just as I thought,
the head is the weak point.
It makes no sense for me to cut it, so the only thing that works is the cancelation by making physical impacts...
It has been a good lesson.
I need to call the special unit so they can clean this mess.
But it’s been a relief that Tosaki-san wasn’t here.
Also, I could protect that girl...
Shit!
He was a decoy...
Was there one more?
This recording is from one month ago.
These are the images from the attack that the laboratory number 2 received.
This is the power from the other species.
Yes, following this incident, we were able to prove the existence of other species.
Yes, following this inicident, we were able to prove the existence of other species.
We’ve confirmed that the incident “Nakamura Shin’ya” was also from another species.
Wait a moment, what happened with the voice? We can’t follow so many new elements.
We’ve come to the conclusion that the voice is a reflex caused by thanatosis.
Reflex from thanatosis?
It’s a defense mechanism that can be seen on insects.
At the moment they receive a stimulus from a superior being,
the muscles get tensed,
and they lose the the ability to move.
However, some countries have never seen
the voice as a threat.
Because we can avoid it by using ear plugs.
Plus, according to some reports, the effect is weaker in humans that are friendly with the Ajin,
or humans that haven’t recognised it as one.
What we should prioritize right now, is–
Shouldn’t you turn it off?
Sorry, there’s an important experiment going on right now.
What? What’s going on?
What do you want?
If it’s about my brother, I don’t know where he is!
It looks like you’re misunderstanding.
We only want to protect Nagai Kei-kun.
Protect?
From what?
From many things.
From the goverment, from the people that want a reward, and from agents from other countries.
I think you experienced it too, some moments ago. There are very dangerous people looking for Kei-kun.
Who are you?
I forgot to introduce myself.
Ajin’s protection committee, Satou-san?
Kei-kun has been put in a very difficult position.
We only want to help him.
Nii-san and...
Um...
Could you also help Nii-san’s accomplice?
Of course.
But only if you cooperate with us.
Understood.
I’ve been thinking about death almost all day.
It’s not weird for me to hallucinate at this point, but...
I’m not losing my head, right?
In any case, I should think what I’ll do from now on.
To begin with, I can’t bring Kai with me.
That’s more than clear.
That’s out of question if I want
to get out of this mountain.
The only thing that’s left to do is to talk to another Ajin.
If I can talk to one, maybe I can get some information.
Nevertheless, in this country there are only 2 Ajin, of which 1 has already been caught by the gover–
No, there must be more. According to the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare.
No, there must be more. According to the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare,
the annual rate of deaths in Japan is greater than a million. Two people die per minute.
There must be hidden Ajin. If I can find them,
I’ll know how to survive without humans.
The only problem is how to get in contact with them.
I’m back.
Oh, welcome back.
What’s wrong?
Ah, nothing...
Anyway, let’s rest until the night.
Let’s take turns each hour.
Sure.
Ah, I forgot.
Here.
Thank you.
Um... Will you really help Kai too?
Yes.
I promise.
Moreover... About what kind of person nii-san is...
Yeah, I’d like to hear that.
I don’t say this because I discovered that Nii-san is an Ajin, but...
If I have to explain it...
You can no longer play with Kaitou-kun.
Why?
If there isn’t a reason, I won’t accept it.
Listen to me, Kaitou-kun is the son of a criminal.
Then, I have no choice.
Besides, I only played with him because it made me sad to see him alone.
Nii-san is the worst.
That’s a pretty original expression.
Is there something more?
Nothing special.
I see, thank you.
This concludes your role.
What?
What do you want?
Another way to get in contact with Ajin is the internet.
But for that, I need to use Kai’s phone, which hasn’t been discovered yet.
But that’s not the only reason why I need his phone.
The other reason is that it’s possible that there are other Ajin looking for me.
If so...
Maybe I could become friends with them...
Eriko-chan
That’s it. Eriko.
But it could also be the police.
Eriko-chan
I don’t think Eriko would snitch about Kai to the police,
but I still need to probe it.
Eriko-chan
The person you’re trying to reach is not available.
Please leave your message after the tone.
Eriko-chan
If it’s a human or an Ajin...
Have you seen a black ghost?
It’s Nagai.
I didn’t think you would answer.
You’re Ajin, right?
Yes, of course.
Why do you have my sister’s phone?
If you want to know, you have to come
to the place we’ll tell you.
Do you have any means of transportation?
Yes.
The Ajin that hide must be of two types.
The ones that hide without drawing attention,
and the ones that make a mess.
The ones that make a mess, when they do something
to people that shouldn’t be affected...
When they do something like that...
I’ll kill them.
I think I’ll die of dehydration.
But if I die now, I’ll revive with the nutrients and necessary water to live again, isn’t it like that?
If I could talk with another Ajin...
Even though they can’t kill me, they could lock me.
But for me, I have nothing left but to meet with them.
What’s that attire?
I’m so sorry, I didn’t have any other clothes.
So I chose the most modest...
Report.
Yes, Nagai Eriko was kidnapped 3 hours ago.
We think that Tanaka and Hat could be...
That doesn’t matter.
I want to know the process and the result from the battle between black ghosts.
Understood.
In first place–
Wait.
It’s Araki from the office in Saitama.
After the kidnap, Nagai Eriko’s phone has been used once.
We have been able to get the location.
Good, follow that signal. The person that called that phone must be someone who tried to get in contact with Nagai Kei.
Understood.
It’s a really quiet place, don’t you think? The monk doesn’t come around often.
And there are almost no guards.
Satou-san and...
Eh?
Kei?
He ran away...
Kai-san!
I think Onii-chan won’t come.
Yeah... he called.
It’s summer again...
I thought that was the fastest way you would believe me.
He’s a real...
I’ll do it too.
No, you’re famous. And so is he.
Tanaka?
The second Ajin in the whole country!
There was no announcement, but... he escaped?
They’re dangerous people.
Ok, it’s time to get to the point.
Just as I said on the phone, we’re ready to help you.
Everything else goes by your own.
Before that, I want to ask you three questions.
They don’t have to be three, you can ask as much as you want.
First, I’d like to know about Eriko.
We have freed her.
Eh?
Everything is alright now. The hospital is close.
She should be on her way to the hospital right now.
I’m so sorry about what I did.
I know this may seem like an excuse, but this was the only way to reach you.
I definitely scared your little sister...
If she’s alright then there’s no problem.
I was just worried. Raise your head, please.
I’m really sorry.  Please continue with that you were saying.
I’m really sorry. Please continue with that you were saying.
Yes.
The second is about your daily life.
I want to know how you live.
You’ve probably been victim of a lot of stuff since people discovered that you are an Ajin.
Yeah, well...
However, I don’t think that you should see all humans beings as your enemies.
To be more human than humans, that’s my motto.
To live calmly. That’s our daily life.
Even though he doesn’t agree too much with that.
What is it that you want to do, Nagai-kun?
It’s true.
It’s true that bad things have happened, and it’s true that there are cruel humans,
but as Satou-san, I don’t want to see humans as enemies.
I only want to live calmly and peacefully.
I’ve understood exactly what you want, Nagai-kun.
However, I want you to memorize this.
I’ve said that my motto is to live in peace.
But things would change if someone tries to trap you or torture you.
In that moment, I’ll make use of my best strategy to get you back.
As I did with him.
Maybe I can trust this person.
So? What’s your third question?
Ah, I’m sorry.
It’s about the black ghost...
It’s a numbness bullet!
The police!
Watch out, Nagai-kun!
Nagai-kun! Wake up! Nagai-kun!
Satou-san, run...
Disapproved.
Well? What should we do?
We need to teach him...
To be continued
Next episode
asks for help
A piece of crap that only
when needed