Mass murders.
The first attack will be next Wednesday at 15:00.
We'll attack the Grand Pharmaceutical buildings.
We are a pharmaceutical company.
We can't rest while so much people are suffering.
I've been escaping from Satou and the government people.
I have to stop him.
You're the one I can't let free,
since you know where I am.
Dumbass! Let me out!
The IBM is strong.
But it has its not perfect.
Now you want to fight, don't you?
Tosaki-senpai is clearly weird.
He knows too much.
We'll make this man work hard for us.
And when push comes to shove...
"We'll make him disappear", he said.
Bring it on.
Strategy is vital for everything.
A certain General said it too.
"I love it when–
–A plan comes together"
Right?
That's right.
This is awesome!
We sure put an effort on this summer homework.
It's a masterpiece.
Well then...
Let's go.
Showtime
Well, It's
We're 2 days away from the attack,
according to the warning from the man known as Satou.
As you can see, the security of Grand Pharmaceutical building has been increased.
Well, well...
Things sure got dangerous outside.
Excuse me...
Ma'am...
I have a favor to ask you.
I think we can get inside in 5 minutes.
We're ready here.
Hi, we're from Clean Fox Services.
This is for the repair of pipes.
Repair of pipes?
Did you hear something?
No, they haven't notified us anything.
This, I got it doing a job.
But the higher ups, seeing that there's no personnel...
It's hard to be another worker.
I understand.
It's an installation?
Yeah.
Ah, there's one scheduled.
Damn...
You're amazing!
On another note, we have to hurry up.
Satou-san, can you see it?
Yeah, the vision is excellent.
Yeah, That's the north wall.
Can I leave it to you?
No problem.
This is the suggestion from the Anti-Ajin committee.
Any questions?
Yeah.
Um... About these water sprinklers...
It's for the IBM.
In one of the latest investigations it was found
that the IBM doesn't go well with water.
How's the security in Grand Pharmaceutical?
Perfect. Since the day of the warning, the entrance has been more restricted.
We've also checked the whole building for possible bombs.
About possible hackings to the system...
We've included the maximum possible security.
I see. Nevertheless, the opponent is Satou.
Do not underestimate him.
Um... Wrapping up, can I ask you something?
What is it?
It's about the way to capture the target...
Uh... Are we seriously... using that method?
Is there any problem with that?
Well... Um... It's strange to say it like that, but...
I think maybe that's too inhumane.
The Ajin aren't human.
That's why a word like "inhumane" can't be applied to them.
Understood...
Okay...
I wish you the best of lucks.
Takahashi-kun, that's upside down.
Shut up!
Gen-kun, open that 20 centimeters more.
Gotcha.
What?
You wanted them, right?
See ya.
Wait, Nagai!
Hey! We really won't do anything?
It will happen the day after tomorrow!
We've already talked about this, haven't we?
We might be able to stop him!
Stop him?
Of course! We have to fight!
I was the dumb one for asking.
Wait!
I know where Satou is hiding!
What if we tell the police?
It's impossible that he'll stay in the same place forever.
He must have moved already.
Especially because you escaped.
Listen, Nagai!
When I met satou, he said he was going to do a genocide!
It doesn't matter whether the police intervenes or not.
Ajin can kill all the people they want.
Satou plans to do it for real!
Maybe.
But if being Ajin allows them to do dangerous things, the same applies to us!
We might be able to stop him!
This doesn't get us anywhere.
First of all, this person must have received military training.
Only fighting him is useless. We don't have any chance of winning.
Then what were you training with that black ghost?
Didn't you plan to fight with it?
I did that out of curiosity.
Also, knowing my aptitudes and weaknesses,
is something I need to know, whether I fight or not.
You...
Seriously won't fight?
I like my current life.
It's peaceful, quiet, and without worries.
I won't quit this life.
As long as you're fine, the rest don't matter?
It's impossible to find someone
that doesn't think that way.
You're the worse.
Dumbass.
Incredible!!
I'm back.
Ah, welcome.
Curry?
As you asked for, beef curry.
I feel so happy...
Ah, right.
Here, you also asked me for this.
So you bought it!
Coincidentally there was one in the city.
That's a present.
Thank you!
I'm sorry for making you spend so much money.
Don't worry for the money.
Men should simply be proud.
Proud.
I'll remember it.
Will you contact someone?
Don't you think it's too early?
If you come out now...
Of course not...
I just wanted to investigate some things.
Oh, well!
If you wanna investigate something, you just have to go to the library.
Kids nowadays are so wrong.
That machine won't teach you anything.
Everything fine?
Perfect.
Looks like everything is ready.
Let's go, Tanaka-kun.
Yeah.
You seem to be having fun.
Tanaka-kun, I...
I always play everything in hard mode.
Why do you tell me that all of a sudden?
The difficulty.
The higher it is, the more enjoyable it is.
President, we should send the employees to their homes.
It's a request from the commissar.
Time is money.
Do you know how many millions of employees I would lose if I stop coming one day?
You're putting lifes in danger!
Life is synonym to money.
If something like the IBM really exist...
What could I do?
I don't know how he plans to attack, but...
It's impossible to do something with all this security.
Understood. Start!
I don't have the time to deal with his foolishness.
Everything is okay.
You're the client with reservations...
You! What are you doing?
You're shaking.
Ah... It can't be.
Uh?
This is crazy!
Nothing new.
He actually did it.
That was top tier!
I-It can't be.
This is a transmission from the Grand Pharmaceutical buildings.
The building!
A taller building has been blown down,
and has destroyed Grand Pharmaceuticals!
Fuck!
It was smashed!
So they come to this.
Thank you, Okuyama-kun.
Well then...
I don't think our enemies will let me get out of here.
How long are you going to wait?
Why don't you call the Anti-Ajin force?
No. That's a group whose existence is illegal.
I can't let them appear in plain sunlight.
The higher ups decided it that way.
We've completely lost.
From now on...
We have to save whoever we can!
It's Satou!
He's making fun of us.
Well, guys...
You don't think this is over, do you?
Who is the strongest force of this country?
The Self-Defence Forces?
Wrong.
Those kids don't even have real combat experience.
Which means...
Exactly.
The Police Special Assault Team.
When terrorism or other extreme delits are committed,
and the police can't handle them,
these guys come to scene.
So, if I beat them, I could name myself the strongest soldier of this country.
I invite you, citizens,
to referee this battle.
We, or the humans.
Who are you siding with?
Tosaki-senpai, the Hat has started his own transmission.
All Japan is watching this battle!
We can't lose!
Neither he.
Okay...
It's show time!
To be continued
Next episode
Tiring!
That was