negai kanau nara mou ichido kimi no kokoro ni furete itai
If I could have my wish granted once more, I would want to touch your heart.
donna yami demo sagashiterunda tada hitotsu no hikari o
No matter what kind of darkness you're in, search for your one and only light.
As I look up to the stars
tooi kedo, onaji hoshizora miageteru
Although we're far apart, I'm looking at the same starry sky as you.
kokoro no sora ni wa kobore ochisouna
In the sky inside of your heart,
kimi no egao to nukumori
your warmth and smile are close to falling apart.
Hear me
Until I went away
And faced the lonely days
and faced the lonely days
ai suru koto mo iminatte
I thought I understood what it meant to love someone.
wakatteta tsumori datta
Feeling everything that was right in front of me.
Feeling everything that was right in front of me
I lost what was most important to me
taisetsu na mono ushinatte
hontou no ai ni kitsuite
And realized it had been true love
I'll tell you now, just how close you are
TENCHOU FANSUBS